A Guide to the Martin Ashton Hutchinson Papers, 1923-1962
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Lois Hall 1948-1950 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Robert E. Hamlet 1944-1945 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Annie Hardaway 1958-1959 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Thomas Harris v. Thalhimers Inc. 1949 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Harris v. Harris 1962 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph H. Harrison 1954 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: George A. Hase 1954-1955 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Hasher v. Hasher 1938-1944, 2 folders (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Marguerite Melenee Hawk 1944 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Edith T. Hawley and husband 1951-1960 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: James H. Hayes 1941-1953 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Hayes Claim, etc. 1962 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: Walter Heenan 1940-1955 (Box 35)
- Legal Case Files: John Dallas Hendricks 1953 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: John Hendricks 1960-1961 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Hermitage Methodist Homes of Virginia 1961 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Walter Herrmann 1958 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: W. H. Hester 1959 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Nathan M. Hobbs 1954-1956 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Nellie S. Hoff 1952-1955 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Frank Hoffman 1959-1960 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: James R. Holland 1949-1961, 3 folders (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: E. A. Holsten, Inc. 1958-1962, 2 folders (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Holsten, Inc. v. Carl and Thelma Jackson 1957-1962 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: E. A. Holsten, Inc. v. Valentino Motors, Inc. 1959 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Holsten, Inc. v. White Furniture and Appliance Co. 1959 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Robert N. Howard 1962 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: John Hrubenski 1962 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Elizabeth K. Hughes 1960 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: Rosemarie Hurley 1962 (Box 36)
- Legal Case Files: H. E. Jackson 1942-1944 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Raymond L. Jackson v. Hodges 1938-1940, 2 folders (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Joe Earnest James 1955-1958 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Virginia S. James v. Roy W. James 1947 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Janitors Better Service Club 1944-1948 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: R. L. Jarrett 1953-1954 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Robert L. and Alma S. Jarrett 1956 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Louis N. Johns' Will 1956 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Johnson v. Johnson 1951-1953 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Mr. and Mrs. J. R. Johnson 1945 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: James R. Johnson 1959 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Mr. and Mrs. Robert A. Johnson v. Earl L. Backos 1948 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Manuel Juranis 1948-1950 (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Jury Instructions n.d. (Box 37)
- Legal Case Files: Marie Sims Kane v. William S. Kane 1954-1955 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Thomas J. and Katherine H. Kelly 1957-1958 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Patricia C. Kennedy 1959-1960 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: George Kepreos 1950-1960 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Kientz v. Kientz 1950-1952 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: King v. King 1946- (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Alfred J. Kirsch 1942 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Kirsch and Bazile 1936-1944, 2 folders (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Kniesche v. Parrish 1941 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Kuhr 1945 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Elizabeth Kirk Lauritzen 1949 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Lauritzen Motors Inc. - Claim against J. E. Fisher 1943-1947 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Lauritzen Motors Inc. v. Roland L. Troxler 1943-1948 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Lauritzen Motors Inc. 1953 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Lauritzen Motors Inc. 1957-1958 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Lauritzen Motors Inc. 1957 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Laura B. Lawton - Isle of Wight Company Matter 1951-1956 (Box 38)
- Legal Case Files: Laura B. Lawton - Isle of Wight Company Matter 1955-1956, 2 folders (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Henry Lee 1942-1945 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Legal Documents ca. 1940-1955 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Bill Lewis 1959-1960 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: F. A. Linker 1942-1951 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Sarah L. Lloyd 1955 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Fred W. Logan 1957-1961 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Martha Logan v. Moss and Stone 1950-1951 (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Lucerne Butter and Cr譥 Company 1940-1943, 2 folders (Box 39)
- Legal Case Files: Lucerne Butter and Cr譥 Company 1941-1948 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Laura Rebecca Lyons 1958 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: R. A. McCarthy 1953 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: E. H. McConnell 1944-1949 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Thelma M. McCoy 1962 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Francis McDermott and wife 1962 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Merle L. McGill 1962 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Fred Nichols McGlocklin 1961 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph D. McGonagle v. J. M. Sadler and Metropolitan Life Insurance Company 1941 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: C. S. McKinney 1973 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: L. C. McPherson 1953 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Mary W. Mann 1951-1952 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Manning v. Manning 1940-1944 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: M. M. Marcuse 1950-1954 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Marks v. Virginia Transit 1949 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Robert W. Mathias 1951-1953 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Adelaide E. Meiser 1961 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Methodist Church 1954-1955 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: Middle Atlantic Mobilehouse Association Committee 1954 (Box 40)
- Legal Case Files: John R. Mills 1955-1957 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: Maurice Mitchell 1950-1953 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: James Ernest Monroe 1952 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: Mooers Motor Car Company 1953-1958 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: Morgan Oil Company 1952 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: Morgan Oil Company v. C. S. Owens 1952-1953 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: Morgan and Supply Company 1955-1962, 4 folders (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: Morrison v. Willis 1945-1946 (Box 41)
- Legal Case Files: John M. Morton, Jr. 1942 October (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Elizabeth Mosby 1942-1944 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: J. C. B. Moseley 1960-1961 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Marzella Moseley 1953-1955 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Lorenzo J. Moss 1941-1942 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Dr. J. C. Moxley 1941-1942 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: National School Supply Company 1948-1950 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Newell, Washington and Henry Lodge 1945 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Robert Lee Norris 1947-1949 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: North American Assurance Company 1940 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: North Highland Park Land Company 1941 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Old Dominion Carnival Workers Union Charter n.d. (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Oriental Restaurant 1956-1960 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Walter Henry Osborne 1953 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Priscilla Owenby 1953-1954 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Owens v. World of Mirth Shows, Inc. 1949-1950 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Charles Palmler v. Andrews 1951 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Palmer v. Palmer 1952 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Parker v. Beard 1942-1943 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Bobby Ray Parker 1962 (Box 42)
- Legal Case Files: Kate Parrish 1961 (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: Louise B. Pavay 1934-1954, 2 folders (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: Pavey v. Pavey 1962 (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: Herman Payne 1953 (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: J. W. Pearson 1945 (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: Ronald H. Peele 1961 (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: Pembroke Water Company 1955-1958, 4 folders (Box 43)
- Legal Case Files: Pembroke Water Company 1957-1958 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Penisula Shipbuilders Association 1950 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Perry v. Bryant 1948 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: E. D. Petrey 1942 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Philips Machinery Company 1953-1955 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Phipps v. Phipps 1941-1943 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Stewart W. Pierce 1950 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Allen W. Pittman v. R. J. Hewitt 1942 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: James C. Porter v. Jim N. Nelms 1953-1956 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Norman G. Preston, Jr. 1962 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: William C. Price 1954 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Jesse W. Pritchard 1955 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Loyd Ranson 1953 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Ray et al. v. Beasley et. Al. 1951-1954 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: George S. Reamey 1949-1951 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Frank M. Reif 1942 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: C. E. Reyna 1958 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: C. E. Richardson 1952 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Richmond Broadcasting Company, Inc. 1948 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Richmond Hotels Inc. 1953-1960 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Harry Charles Robelen 1946-1956 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Charles Robertson 1942 (Box 44)
- Legal Case Files: Rosedale Association 1960-1961 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: David M. Rosen 1951 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Rowsey - Virginia Commission for the Blind 1945-1946, 2 folders (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Albert F. Rumph 1961 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: William Carter Russell 1961 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: O. B. Rust, Jr. and Midland Acceptance Corporation 1959-1960 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Dillie Lee Ryan 1944 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Satterwhite v. Groome 1949-1950 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Earl K. Saunders 1957 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: C. S. Savage 1947-1947, 2 folders (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: William S. Scarborough, Jr. 1962 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph Schenker 1945-1948 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph Schenker 1951 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph Schenker v. Duke and Son 1954-1955 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Schenker v. Sydnor-Hundley 1954 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Alice Henry Schlater 1947-1948 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Mary E., R. L. Schutte 1953 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Robert D. Schutte 1957 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Robert L. Schutte 1959 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Schutte Case 1958 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: William A. Schwertfeger 1947 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Robert Leslie Scribner 1957 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: William Seid 1947 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Shamrock Trucking Company 1955 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Chong Shaw 1956 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Charles Joseph Sheerin 1954 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Palmer A. Shelburne 1937-1941 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: C. I. Sheppard 1941 (Box 45)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Rebecca H. Shepherd 1948; 1955 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Shepherd's Citations File 1958-1959 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Beverley B. Shumaker 1961 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Sibley 1962 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Raymond Siegfried v. Independent Cab Company 1940 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Troy C. Sigmon 1961-1962 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Sterling Simpson 1958 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph I. Sims and Mrs. Taylor 1961 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Sixth Mount Zion Baptist Church 1938-1945, 5 folders (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Dr. Ira M. Smith v. Chaplain 1936-1937 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: John A. Smith 1941-1944 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: William P. Smith 1961 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Smith v. Lawrence 1942-1945 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Gerald Snellens 1949-1950 (Box 46)
- Legal Case Files: Thomas S. Soles 1943 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: R. L. Sowers 1945 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: R. Pinkey Sowers 1943 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: R. P. Sowers 1957 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Sowers v. Whitehead 1946-1949 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Inez M. Sprinkel 1953-1954 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Clyde Stanley et. al. v. Rowe 1941 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: John W. Stanley 1953-1957 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: E. E. Staples v. Sheffield Transfer Company 1939-1945 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. M. M. Staples 1953-1954, 1962 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: John E. Stefaniga et al. v. Fornash Construction Company 1953-1954 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Lawrence Stephenson 1955 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Jean Ellen Stewart 1948 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Minnie Purvis Stoneman 1954-1962 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: F. C. Stover 1937-1940 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Stratton 1934-1935 (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Strickland v. Payne 1941-1942, 2 folders (Box 47)
- Legal Case Files: Charles Stuart 1949-1951 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Lydia C. Stuples 1958 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Louise C. Sully 1948 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Louise C. Sully 1960 July 15 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Rose Elizabeth Sully 1942-1948 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Thomas H. Sykes 1951 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Talbott v. Gray 1941-1948 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Harold Tanner and Mack Davis v. Herbert S. Wilburn 1938-1942 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Layetta E. Taylor 1948-1949 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: M. C. Taylor 1941-1943 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: McCarthy Taylor 1951-1952 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: S. F. Taylor 1943 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Maude Teter 1960-1961 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Clifford Thacker 1959 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Thomas and Talley 1941-1943 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Mr. and Mrs. Clifford Elton Thacker 1953 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: A. Thornhill 1943-1946 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Arthur Upshur Tiller 1945 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Tilless and Childress 1942-1943 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: A. B. Timberlake 1934 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Timberlake Service Center v. Fornash Construction Company 1953 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Mrs. Florence L. Trant 1950 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: J. M. Turner v. C. H. Admas 1958 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: William v. Turner 1961 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Turner Estate 1950 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Turret Checking System Inc. 1947 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Tushin v. Yellow Cab Company 1945-1946 (Box 48)
- Legal Case Files: Dora McGill Taylor 1955, 3 folders (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Undertakers Association - Virginia Funeral Directors Association, Inc. 1938-1941 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Charlotte Upton 1944 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: T. C. Utterback 1953-1954 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Glenda Vaughan 1956 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Vick 1958-1959 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Virginia Corporation Law 1950 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Virginia Electric Employees Association 1961 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Virginia Methodist Children's Home 1962 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Virginia Mutual Benefit Life Insurance Company 1946 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Ben Walker 1941-1942 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Robert Walker 1943 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Margaret Elizabeth Wash 1942-1943 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Mortimer Watkins v. J. C. Bruner 1940-1941 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: Weaver v. World of Mirth Shows 1948-1949 (Box 49)
- Legal Case Files: William J. Weis 1953 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Richard W. Wekenman 1944 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Edna L. and Lena A. Welchlin 1961 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Frank West 1955-1956 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Miss Lula West 1945-1946 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: West Disinfecting Company v. United States 1939-1942 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Joseph Carter White 1947 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Richard Lewis Wilcox 1955-1961 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Charles C. Wilkes v. Rice M. Youell 1932 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Dorothy Lawrence Wilinson v. Archie E. Wilkinson 1943 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Willett Brothers Transportation Company 1951 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Don W. Williams 1959 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Don W. Williams and wife 1961 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: John W. Williams Memorial Fund 1934-1944, 2 folders (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Thomas A. Williams 1942-1944 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Willis v. Willis 1961 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Wills and Trusts 1958 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Alfred Wilson 1951 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Mark Wilson 1947-1948 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Ruth Wilson v. Emmett Wilson 1947 (Box 50)
- Legal Case Files: Winston Heirs 1943 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: Lloyd Nelson Wise 1946 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: Won You Leong - New China Restaurant 1951 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: David Woo v. Lovenstein 1948-1950 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: M. H. Wood 1943-1944 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: P. S. Wood 1957-1962 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: C. H. Woodward 1943 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: A. Chester Wooldridge 1944-1945 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: John H. Woolfolk 1947 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: John H. Woolfolk 1957 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: W. H. Woolfolk 1943-1944 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: World of Mirth Shows, Inc. 1940-1941, 2 folders (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: World of Mirth Shows, Inc. re: Gerald Raymond 1942-1950 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: World of Mirth Shows, Inc. 1943 (Box 51)
- Legal Case Files: yeager v. Bowers 1962 (Box 52)
- Legal Case Files: Ligh Park Yipp 1946-1956, 4 folders (Box 52)
- Legal Case Files: Walter S. Young 1958 (Box 52)
- Legal Case Files: Zonenint Matter 1960-1961 (Box 52)
- "Veterans for Hutchinson Program" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-219
- "Frank Ball" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-220
- "Martin Hutchinson" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-221
- "Martin Hutchinson" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-222
- "Veterans for Hutchinson Program" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-223
- "Martin Hutchinson" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-224
- "Martin Hutchinson" 1946
  Phonograph Recordings: Campaign Speeches by Martin A. Hutchinson P-225